Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan) publications 1859-2015
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
[Law School (University of Michigan) publications]
1859-2015
University of Michigan--Law School.
Includes addresses and lectures, annual reports, bibliographies, brochures and pamphlets, bulletins and college catalogs, and directories. Also includes histories such as The Law School, 1940-1973; Legal Education at Michigan, 1859-1959; and A Short History and Some of the Graduate of the Department. Also contains journals such as the Michigan Journal of International Law
9784 Bimu C61 2
24 linear feet
1.98 MB
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit (Donor no. 343 ).
The publications group is open to research, except for certain directories, which are restricted.
Please consult the history found in the finding aid for the
Law School (University of Michigan) Records
.
The Publications series of the Law School is divided into four subseries: Unit Publications, Sub-Unit Publications, Topical Publications and Student Publications. Some publications (or their successors) may no longer be available in print but are available in digital format through the law School's archived or current website or in Deep Blue, the university's institutional repository. Links to digital content is provided in the detailed contents list.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Law School.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Law.; Barristers Society (University of Michigan); Law Quadrangle (University of Michigan); University of Michigan. Dept. of Law.; Barristers Society (University of Michigan)
Publications
Law School photographic roster.; Law School, 1940-1973.; Michigan journal of international law.; Law quadrangle notes.; Codicil.; Res gestae.
Genre/Form:
Lectures.; Annual reports.; Bibliographies.; Pamphlets.; Bulletins.; Catalogs, College.; Directories.; Histories.; Scholarly periodicals.; Manuals.; Newsletters.; Proceedings.; Programs.; Reports.; Schedules.; School yearbooks.
- Printed Materials
  - Unit Publications
    Unit Publications include addresses, several of which were given at graduation ceremonies; annual reports; bulletins (course catalogs); directories of students, alumni, faculty and staff; journals and manuals for faculty and students; newsletters, including a run of the newsletter r Law Quadrangle Notes, and printed versions of the on-line newsletter The Docket; various reports; and yearbooks. There are 6 histories of the law school or a component there of, including one by Elizabeth Gaspar Brown titled The Law School of the University of Michigan 1859-1984: An Intellectual History. Note that beginning in November 2002 the authoritative source for program degree requirements is the printed bulletins with effective dated updates in a digital file accessible at http://deepblue.lib.umich.edu/handle/2027.42/86079. Also note that Bentley holdings of the Michigan Law Review are separately cataloged and that the full complete run is maintained by the University of Michigan Law Library.
    - Addresses
      - Address by Hon. Thomas M. Cooley and Poem by Bethune Duffield, Esq. on the Dedication of the Law Lecture Hall, 1863 (Box 1)
      - An Address Delivered Before the Alumni and Students of the Law Department, 1894 (Box 1)
      - An Address to the Graduating Class of the Law Department, 1861 (Box 1)
      - Address to the Graduating Class of the Law Department of the University of Michigan, 1872 (Box 1)
      - Address Upon Law Schools and Legal Education, 1859 (Box 1)
      - Closing Address Delivered to the Senior Class of the Law Department, 1875 (Box 1)
      - Disinterested Public Service, 1891 (Box 1)
      - Farewell Address to the Senior Class of, 1896 (Box 1)
      - The George M. Humphrey Program in Law and Economic Policy: Inaugural Lecture, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Hints to Young Lawyers: An Address Delivered to the Senior Class of the Law Department, 1870 (Box 1)
      - Law Abridgment: Closing Address Delivered Before the Graduating Law Class, 1879 (Box 1)
      - Law and Lawyers in Society: An Address Delivered Before the Graduating Class of the Law Department, 1866 (Box 1)
      - Law as an Educating Force: An Address Delivered at the Annual Commencement at the Law and Dental Schools, 1884 (Box 1)
      - The Legal Profession in America: An Address before the Class of, 1865; 1866 (Box 1)
      - Memorial Discourse: Address on Thomas McIntyre Cooley, 1899 (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1866-1890 (Box 1)
        (Bound Volume of Bulletins and Addresses)
      - Post-war Thinking About the Rule of Law, 1960 (Box 1)
      - Practical Suggestions, 1869 (Box 1)
      - On the Study of Law: An Address at the Opening of the Law Department, 1859 (Box 1)
      - The Supreme Court of the United States, 1887 (Box 1)
      - Synopsis of Lectures on Patent Laws of the United States, 1901 (Box 1)
      - The Wells Memorial, 1891 (Box 1)
    - Annual Reports
      (Report to the President)
      - 1953-1978, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Bibliographies
      - Contributions to Legal Literature in Book Form by Persons Connected with the Law School of the University of Michigan: 1859-1981 (Alphabetic Order), by Elizabeth Gaspar Brown (Box 1)
      - Contributions to Legal Literature in Book Form by Persons Connected with the Law School of the University of Michigan: 1859-1981 (Chronological Order), by Elizabeth Gaspar Brown (Box 1)
      - Law School Faculty Bibliography, 1859-1993, compiled by Beth A. McWilliams, edited by Beth A. McWilliams and Jennifer Lentz, 1995 (Box 1)
      - Publications and Research Projects of Law School Faculty, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Booklets
      - Faculty Scholarship 1999-2002 (Box 1)
    - Brochures
      - Advanced Legal Studies
        - 1961-1965 (Box 1)
        - 1996-2006 (Box 1)
      - Advanced Legal Studies for Foreign Students, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
      - Dual Degree FAQ, 2010 (Box 1)
      - General, 1956-2006; undated (Box 1)
      - The Graduate Program of the Law School, undated (Box 1)
      - Joint Degree Programs, 2001-2006; undated (Box 1)
      - Law Alumni Reunion and Forum, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
      - Legal Education at Michigan, 1949-1955 (Box 1)
      - Recruiting at the University of Michigan Law School, 1983-1991 (Box 1)
      - Research and Graduate Study for Persons from Other Lands, undated (Box 1)
      - Secrets of the Successful Law Student: the Insider's Guide to Year One, undated (Box 1)
    - Bulletins (Degree Program Requirements)
      - 1859-2000, 21 folders (Box 2)
        - (1884/85-1890/91 will be found under the heading "Addresses, Miscellaneous" in Box 1) (Box 2)
      - 2000-2004/05, 3 folders (Box 3)
      - The Curriculum, 2006-2012 (Box 3)
      - Updates to Academic Regulations
        - Juris Doctor Program
          (BHL deposit ID 9784_0001)
          - As of, November 2002
          - As of, May 2005
          - As of, April 2007
          - As of, January 2008
          - As of, May 2009
          - As of, May 2010
          - As of, August 2011
        - Doctor of Science of Law
          - As of August 2003 and revised April 2004, 2003-2004
          - As of April 2006 effective November 4, 1994, 1994-2006
          - As of April 2006 effective July 2003, 2003-2006
        - Master of Comparative Law and Master of Laws Programs, 2005; .PDF file
      - Summer Session
        - Bulletins and 1962-67, 1895-1951; 4 folders (Box 3)
        - Schedule of Work, 1923-1965; 2 folders (Box 3)
        - Special Summer School for Lawyers, 1960-1962 (Box 3)
    - By-Laws
      - Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 3)
    - Catalogs
      - Faculty Course Descriptions, 1979 (Box 3)
      - Subjects and Regulations Concerning Theses, 1899/1900-1908/09, undated (Box 3)
    - Directories
      - Alumni Directory 1860-1941 (Box 3)
      - Alumni Directory 1860-1950, 1951 (Box 3)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1959 (Box 3)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1970 (Box 3)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1981 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1985 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1992 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-1997 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Directory 1859-2002 (Box 4)
      - Directory of New Students, 1982-1985 (Box 4)
      - Face Book, 1996-2007, 6 folders (Box 4)
      - First Year Class, 1967-1981 (Box 4)
      - Foreign Alumni, Visiting Professors and Research Scholars and U.S. Alumni Abroad, 1974-1982 (Box 4)
      - Graduates of the Law Department of the University of Michigan: A Record 1860-1875 (Box 4)
      - International Alumni Directory, 1991 (Box 4)
      - Law School Photographic Roster: First Year, Transfer and Graduate Students, 1980-1995; undated; 4 folders (Box 5)
      - Prudentia in Persona: Delicto in Flagrante, undated (Box 5)
      - Roster of Student Services and Activities, 1979-1984/85, undated (Box 5)
      - Student/Faculty Directory
        - 1965/66-1979/80, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Student Directory
        - 1988-2000, 2 folders (Box 5)
        - 2013-2015, 2 volumes (Box 5)
      - Faculty
        - 2003-2011, 3 folders (Box 5)
      - University of Michigan Legal Directory, 1914 (Box 5)
    - Flyers
      - General, 1965; 1996; undated (Box 5)
    - Histories
      - Historical Summary of Named Professorships, 1980 (Box 5)
      - International Law at Michigan: The First Seventeen Decades, [1991] (Box 5)
      - The Law School 1940-1973, undated (Box 5)
      - The Law School of the University of Michigan 1859-1984 An Intellectual History, 1985 (Box 5)
      - Legal Education at Michigan 1859-1959 (Box 5)
      - A Short History and Some of the Graduates of the Department of Law, 1908 (Box 5)
    - Honors Convocation, 1969-1985; 1995-1996; 2002-2005; 2009-2011
    - Invitations
      - December Law School Brunch, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
      - Dedication of Law Library Addition, 1981 (Box 6)
      - Honors Convocation, 1981-1983 (Box 6)
      - Law School Senior Day, 1974-1993; 1996-2001 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Law Preview Weekend, undated (Box 6)
    - Journals
      - Journal of Law Reform, 1985-2005 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Journal of Gender and Law, Volume 1, No.1, 1993 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Journal of International Law, (In Memoriam of William W. Bishop, Jr.), 1989 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Journal of Race and Law
        (Full journal run maintained by the University of Michigan Law Library.)
        - Volume 1, No.1, 1996 (Box 6)
        - Programs and Schedule of Events, 2005 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Law Journal
        - Volumes 1-4, 1892-1895; 4 folders (Box 6)
      - Michigan Law Review
        (separately cataloged)
        - Programs, Schedule of Events, 2000-2005 (Box 6)
      - Prospectus: A Journal of Law Reform, 1969; 1970 (Box 6)
    - Journal Sponsored Activities
      - Michigan Journal of Race and Law
        - Constitution Making in South Africa, 1997 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Journal of International Law
        - Post-Cold War International Security Threats: Terrorism, Drugs, and Organized Crime, 1999 (Box 6)
    - Lectures
      - Freedom of Speech and the University, Lee C. Bollinger, July 1989 (Box 6)
      - Lectures on Jurisprudence, 1894 (Box 6)
      - Flyers announcing Special Lectures, undated (Box 6)
      - Outline and Class Notes: Hall's Cases, Constitutional Law, 1916 (Box 6)
    - Manuals
      - Academic Regulations, 1965-1979 (Box 6)
      - Admissions Guide, 1971/72 (Box 6)
      - Application and Admission Information, 1991-2006; 2009-2011; 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Cases and Commentary: Survival at the University of Michigan Law School, undated (Box 6)
      - Faculty Handbook, 1984-1994; 2001; 2003 (Box 6)
      - Law School Student Handbook, 1979-1995 (Box 7)
      - Grading Regulations, 1928 (Box 7)
      - Law Students' Handbook, 1954-1965 (Box 7)
      - Orientation Handbook, 1978 (Box 7)
      - Preparation for Law School, undated (Box 7)
      - Rules of Conduct and Disciplinary Procedures, undated (Box 7)
      - Suggestions to College Students Preparing to Study Law, 1953; 1969 (Box 7)
    - Memorials
      - Wade H. McCree, Jr, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Newsletters
      - CLUE: [Computing Newsletter], 1992-1995 (Box 7)
      - The Docket
        - 1978-2001, 13 folders (Box 7)
        - 2001-2005, 3 folders (Box 8)
        - 2003-2005 (Box 8)
      - Law Quadrangle Notes
        - Vol. [1]-31, 1957-1987; 12 folders (Box 8)
          (Includes Law School Fund Reports)
        - Vol. 33-52, 1988-2009; 17 folders (Box 9)
        - Vol. 53-54, 2010-2011; 2 folders (Box 10)
        - 2012 (Box 10)
        - 2015 (Box 10)
      - Quad Angles, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Proceedings
      - International Legal Studies, 1959-1981 (Box 10)
      - Proceedings of the Law Institute, 1939; 1 folders (Box 10)
      - Proceedings of the Law Institute, 1940; 1 folders (Box 10)
    - Programs
      - Banquets, 1909-1964 (Box 10)
      - An Evening in Celebration of the Life of Elizabeth A. Long, 1998 (Box 10)
      - Class Day Exercises, 1888-1923 (Box 10)
      - Commencement, 1866-1904 (Box 10)
      - Presentation of the Portrait of Wilber M. Brucker, 1960 (Box 10)
      - Senior Day, 1966-1995; 1998-2011; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Reports (Box 11)
      - The Assaulted Wife: "Catch 22" Revisited (A Preliminary Overview of Wife Beating in Michigan), 1974 (Box 11)
      - Faculty Comments on Courses, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
      - The Law School in 1934 (Box 11)
      - Law School of the University of Michigan (in The Green Bag), 1889 (Box 11)
      - An Outside Educator Views Michigan's Legal Education from the Inside, undated (Box 11)
      - Report of the Law School, 1930/31-1936/37 (Box 11)
      - A Report on Graduate Studies at the University of Michigan Law School, 1991 (Box 11)
      - Class Schedule, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
      - Final Examination Schedule, 1975-1979 (Box 11)
    - Schedules
      - Final Room Changes, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Schedule of Work
        - 1896/97-1968, 6 folders (Box 11)
    - Yearbooks
      - (The Quad), 1952-1966; 9 folders (Box 11)
      - (The Codicil), 1968-1971; 4 folders (Box 11)
      - (The Codicil), 1972-1981; 4 folders (Box 12)
      - , (The Quadrangle), 1988-1990; 1992; 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Res Ipsa Loquitur, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Sub-Unit Publications
    Sub-Unit Publications consist of materials produced by units within or affiliated with the Law School. These include the Admissions Office, the American Judicature Society, the Financial Aid Office, the Institute of Continuing Legal Education, the Lawyers Club, the Legal Research Institute, the Legislative Research Center, the Michigan Law School Fund, the Placement Office, the Thomas M. Cooley Lectures and the William W. Cook Foundation.
    - Admissions Office
      - Annual Reports, 1961-1978 (Box 12)
      - Brochures
        - General, 1970-1999; undated (Box 12)
        - Linking the Visions, 2003 (Box 12)
    - American Judicature Society
      - Journals
        - Journal of the American Judicature Society, 1927-1953; 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Atomic Energy Research Project
      - Reports
        - International Control of Nuclear Maritime Activities, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Audio Visual Office
      - Form, undated (Box 12)
    - Center for International and Comparative Law
      - Brochures, 1998; circa 2003 (Box 12)
      - Calendar, 1999-2001 (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1999-2004 (Box 12)
    - Child Advocacy Law Clinic
      - Brochure, undated (Box 12)
    - Child Welfare Law Program
      - Brochures, undated (Box 12)
      - Journals, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
    - Clarence Darrow Death Penalty Defense College
      - Brochures, 2001-2005 (Box 12)
    - Clinical Programs
      - Brochures, undated (Box 12)
    - Criminal Law Society
      - Schedule of Events, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Development and Alumni Relations
      - Brochures
        - General, 1976; 1989; undated (Box 12)
        - Reunions, 1994-2009 (Box 12)
      - Giving and Scholarship Funding Recognition (Box 13)
        - Cabinet Honor Rolls
          - Dean's Cabinet, 1991-1996 (Box 13)
          - L. Hart Wright and Paul G. Kauper, undated (Box 13)
        - General, 1995-2001; undated (Box 13)
        - Law School Campaign, 1992-1995 (Box 13)
        - Programs, 2004-2006 (Box 13)
        - Report of Giving, 2001-2007 (Box 13)
      - Newsletters
        - The Law School Connection, 1998 (Box 13)
    - Environmental Law Society
      - Newsletters
        - ELS Newsletter, 1985 (Box 13)
      - Program, 2001 (Box 13)
    - Financial Aid Office
      - Brochures
        - General, 1957; undated (Box 13)
        - Financial Aid Instructions for 2nd and 3rd Year Students, 1971/72 (Box 13)
        - Financial Aids Report, 1971/72-1972/73 (Box 13)
    - Institute of Continuing Legal Education
      - Brochures, undated (Box 13)
      - Bulletins
        - ICLE Bulletin, 1968-1976 (Box 13)
        - ICLE Focus, 1989; 1993 (Box 13)
        - ICLE News, 1966-1974 (Box 13)
    - International and Graduate Office
      - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 13)
    - International Legal Studies
      - Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
      - Issues of Transnational Legal Practice, Volume 7, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Law Library
      - Booklets
        - Dedicatory Exhibit: The Joseph and Edythe Jackier Rare Book Room, 1996 (Box 13)
        - A Guide to Legal Research in the University of Michigan Law Library (Box 13)
      - Brochures, undated (Box 13)
      - Programs
        - Dedication: Law Library Addition, 1981 (Box 13)
        - The Legalization of American Society: A Symposium Commemorating the Dedication of the Law Library Addition, 1981 (Box 13)
      - Reports
        - Automation for the University of Michigan Law Library, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Law School Student Senate
      - Brochures, undated (Box 13)
      - Directories
        - Law School Student Senate Directory, 1977/78 (Box 13)
      - Reports
        - Michigan Law Critique, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Lawyers Club
      - Addresses
        - Addresses Delivered at the Dedication of the Lawyers Club, 1925 (Box 13)
      - Brochures, 1930-1957; undated (Box 13)
      - Certificates, 1995 (Box 13)
      - Handbooks
        - 1925/26-1949/50, 10 folders (Box 13)
        - 1950/51-1984/85, 7 folders (Box 14)
      - Histories
        - The Lawyers Quadrangle, 1931 (Box 14)
      - Proceedings
        - Founder's Day Dinner, 1939-1950 (Box 14)
      - Regulations
        - Lawyers Club Rules, 1965/66 (Box 14)
      - Reports
        - The University of Michigan Lawyers Club (In The Phi Alpha Delta Quarterly), 1925 (Box 14)
        - The University of Michigan Lawyers Club Dining Hall, 1970 (Box 14)
      - Yearbooks
        - The Brief of the Lawyers Club, 1925 (Box 14)
    - Leadership Program
      - Brochures, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Legal Assistance for Urban Communities Program
      - Booklets
        - Celebrating Ten Years: Assisting Detroit Communities Turn Inspiration into Reality, 2001 (Box 14)
      - Guides
        - Guide to Financial Resources for Community Development Corporations, 1995 (Box 14)
      - Manuals
        - Land Acquisition Procedures Manual, 2000 (Box 14)
        - Personnel Policies Manual for Michigan Nonprofit Corporations, 1996 (Box 14)
      - Pamphlets, 1991; undated (Box 14)
      - Final Report to the Rockefeller Foundation, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Legal Research Institute
      - Reports
        - Discovery Before Trial, 1932 (Box 14)
    - Legislative Research Center
      - Reports
        - Annexation: A Solution to the Metropolitan Area Problem, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Law School Fund
      - Brochures, 1970-1987 (Box 14)
      - Manuals
        - Worker's Handbook, undated (Box 14)
      - Reports will be found interfiled with the Law Quadrangle Notes under the heading "Unit Publications, Newsletters" (Box 14)
    - Office of Career Services
      - Booklets
        - Careers, 2003 (Box 14)
        - Paths, 2006 (Box 14)
      - Brochures
        - Recruiting, 2001-2004 (Box 14)
    - Office of Public Interest Programs
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Office of Public Service
      - Brochures, 2005 (Box 14)
      - Flyers, 2005 (Box 14)
      - Newsletters
        - The Public Service Newsletter, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Order of the Coif
      - Certificates, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Placement Office
      - Brochures, 1967-1972 (Box 14)
      - Directories
        - Placement Directory, 1968-1980 (Box 14)
      - Manuals
        - Placement, 1969/70-1978/79 (Box 14)
      - Reports
        - Placement Reports, 1961/62-1978/79 (Box 14)
    - Prisoner Legal Advocacy Project
      - Flyers, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Student Computer Lab
      - Newsletters
        - Upload: Law Computer Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - William W. Bishop Lectures in International Law
      - Programs, 1998-2004 (Box 14)
    - William W. Cook Foundation
      - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 14)
      - Articles from Law Quad Notes about William W. Cook, 2006 (Box 14)
      - Lectures
        - First Series
          - Freedom and Responsibility in the American Way of Life, 1944 (Box 14)
        - Third Series
          - Alternative to Serfdom, 1947 (Box 14)
        - Fourth Series
          - Men and Measures in the Law, 1948 (Box 14)
        - Fifth Series (Box 15)
          - Characteristically American, 1948 (Box 15)
        - Eighth Series
          - The Politics of Industry, 1955 (Box 15)
      - Programs, 1944-1998 (Box 15)
    - The Thomas M. Cooley Lectures
      - Flyer, 1949 (Box 15)
      - Lectures
        - First Series
          - The Constitution and Socio-Economic Change, 1948 (Box 15)
        - Second Series
          - Some Problems of Equity, 1950 (Box 15)
        - Fifth Series
          - A Common Lawyer Looks at the Civil Law, 1955 (Box 15)
        - Sixth Series
          - Public Policy and the Dead Hand, 1955 (Box 15)
        - Seventh Series
          - Frontiers of Constitutional Liberty, 1956 (Box 15)
        - Ninth Series
          - Law and Social Process in United States History, 1960 (Box 15)
      - Programs, 1949-1997 (Box 15)
  - Alumni Publications
    Alumni Publications include information about Law School alumni, their reunions and organizations. The Alumni Survey, Classes of 1873 through 1995, the International Alumni Reunion, the Michigan Black Law Alumni Society, the Michigan Law Alumni Reunion, Minority Alumni weekends, and the Minority Affairs Summer Program are included in this series.
    - Alumni Survey
      - Reports, 1952-1968 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1873
      - Reports
        - First Reunion of the Law Class of 1873 (Includes History and Directory), 1903 (Box 15)
        - Secretary's Preliminary Report for the Fortieth Anniversary Reunion, 1913 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1883
      - Histories
        - History of Law Class of 1883 of Michigan University (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1886
      - Directories, 1911-1936 (Box 15)
      - Reports
        - Minutes of Reunion, 1911-1941 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1887
      - Newsletters
        - Class Annual, 1888-1901 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1890
      - Directories, 1893-1895 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1891
      - Directories, 1911-1941 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1892
      - Directories
        - Class of 1892,1942 (Box 15)
        - Columbian Law Class, 1901 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1893
      - Anthologies
        - Memories of '93, 1928 (Box 15)
      - Directories, 1901-1903; undated (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1894
      - Directories
        - Law Class of 'Ninety-Four, 1916-1933 (Box 15)
        - Our Book: On Induction to Emeritus Class of University of Michigan in June 1946 the Members of the Law Class of 1894 Tell of Their Activities and Experiences During the First Fifty Years Following Their Graduation and Admission to the Bar in 1894 (Box 15)
      - Newsletters
        - The Bulletin